Can we please just stop saying "coitus"?
(Sheldon:)Technically,
that would be coitus interruptus.
(Penny:)Hey, is there a trick
to getting it to switch from tub to shower?
(Penny:)Oh, hi, sorry.
(Penny:)Hello.
Enchanté, mademoiselle.
(Howard:)Howard Wolowitz,
CalTech Department of Applied Physics.
(Howard:)You may be familiar
with some of my work.
(Howard:)It's currently orbiting
Jupiter's largest moon...
(Howard:)...taking high-resolution
digital photographs.
(Penny:)Penny. I work at
The Cheesecake Factory.
(Leonard:)- I'll show you the trick with the shower.
- Okay.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
(Penny:)I'm sorry?
It's French for "good shower."
(Howard:)It's a sentiment I can express
in six languages.
(Leonard:)Save it for your blog, Howard.
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
LEONARD: All right, there it goes.
It sticks, I'm sorry.
- Okay, thanks.
- You're welcome.
Oh, you're just gonna step right...? Okay.